Big talking point was the two penalties.
It's clear, it's clear as day.
I don't know what more you want him to do.
If he picked the ball up with two hands, are you going to give penalty then or not?
But I think when we try to talk to the referee, and then he just tells us to focus on
the AFC.
How can the referee say this? We're talking about now.
He said, "Focus on the AFC."
But, I mean, if you want me to go deeper, I can go deeper, but it might get me in
trouble.
I'm a man that says it how it is.
And yeah, I think it's clear talking points with the referee. His mind is elsewhere. The referee said this?
The fourth referee after the match said this?
During the checking this, he said, "Just focus on the MC," the moment we were asking him to check
and go back to the bar and check. He said.
His earpiece is recording, so I hope he picked this up, but maybe it's switched off at that point.
I don't know. Do you think you were wronged by the referee? It wasn't fair.
I mean, you see this, there's two penalties.
For me, the first one, clear penalty. Everyone sees this.
In an unnatural position, it's a penalty.
Throughout the season, clear penalty. But now we get to close crunch time, they change it.
I don't know why. The last question is for the benefit of those who are wronged by the judge.
If you said that we are wronged today, why are you angry?
No, that's my nature, I'm excited. No, no. Okay. No, no.
This is me, on the contrary, always like this. We know who. Who are we chasing?
Will the other teams oppress you through the judge?
Listen, at the end of the day, we win and we lose together.
And we lose gracefully.
We don't get too low with the lows, and we don't get too high with the highs.
But we move on, we do what we can do.
And hopefully we get some decisions and some fair ones and the right ones.
Last question, sorry, Tony. Do you still have hope in the tournament? Of course. If we have..
Good referees and we play how we normally play and decisions go our way.
We have a good chance, but when it's like this, it's always going to be tough.
but we can just concentrate on ourselves. And who knows what?
We always meet him and we were happy with him in the family game today.
Maybe the team was tight because he was tight. So no. I'm Blacks.
I'm never nervous, I lose happy and I win happy.
You know, same, same, no problem, it's within here. We love his smile.